Blessed by heaven and earth
the Chaos Pearl was born
The Supreme Lord split it into two
The celestial energy within
became the Spirit Pearl
while the demonic energy
formed the Demon Orb
A Wrath of Heaven curse
was cast on the Demon Orb
set to destroy it with lightning
in three years
Later,
due to Shen Gongbao's intervention
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha,
the third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing,
also the third son of the Loong King
By fate
the two became best friends
Nezha, influenced by his parents
shed his demonic nature
and saved Chentang Pass
Together with Ao Bing
they faced the Wrath of Heaven
and at last
changed their destinies
Though you survived the wrath
your bodies were destroyed...
without which
your souls will soon fade
into oblivion
The Sacred Lotus protects
and nurtures spirit
I will now use it to recreate
your physical forms
- Wow
- Stunning
Let's start!
Something's off...
Is there?
The lotus root must be powdered
to make your bodies
Did you just scratch your feet
with that hand?
Oh, don't worry
I don't mind sticky foot,
a quick wash will fix it
It's not your foot that I care
Did you just blow your nose
with that hand?
No, nothing
It's just lotus powder
See?
Lotus powder
It's ready to go
Here, come on
One booger for each of you
I mean one serving
Chop-chop! To save your souls
I'd rather...
Pain in the ass, little jerk!
It works!
Hang on
What is this?
Thank you
I've been looking all over for it
Time for shaping
Flying Pig's memory is unmatched
so is his carving skills
It's perfect, right?
Thanks, Piggy
Don't move,
the body has not been fixed yet
Master Immortal
I've mobilized all
of Chentang's forces
to fend off Shen Gongbao
and the Eastern Sea Loongs
Take it easy
The Loongs are watching
the Abyss monsters
none of which would escape
Shen Gongbao alone is no threat
You should check this out
Isn't this impeccable?
He learned from the best
But
does it have to be exactly the same?
Can't you make me look better?
Huh?
That's right
Parents always want
the best for kids, huh?
Right
Make me tall and hunky
Also hauntingly handsome
A man must be strong and lofty
As well as demure and mindful
But also cute and lovable
Can you all make up your mind?
Tall and hunky
With a touch of handsomeness
Strong and lofty
Yet super adorable
What's this?
Start your performance
Come on!
I should've taken over earlier
DIY is always the best
This could take a while
Let's do you first
You were born of the water element
so you must be tempered
by pure water
Open Lotus!
Here we go
Are you done?
Almost
This version is surely
the most dazzling
but fine-tuning will
take a long time
How about we just use
the first one for now?
Yeah, the first version will do
I agree
Right
You were born of the fire element
so you must be refined
in pure flames
Sir!
Enemy has been spotted at sea
It seems to be Shen Gongbao
- How many?
- Just him
How come?
Carry on with your spell
We'll handle the intruder
Master Immortal
let me go plead with my master
Don't move! Before another
incense stick is fully burnt
your body won't be fixed
Shen Gongbao
to what do we owe this honor?
Now that you know
of my plan with the Loongs
I can't help but feel un...uneasy
Chentang Pass is heavily guarded
and Master Taiyi is within the city
You, alone, won't accomplish much
Who... who said I'm alone?
If they find out
about the Spirit Pearl
not only will you fail
to avenge your son
but the entire Eastern Loong Clan
will bear the blame
When the truth comes out
you'll be cast
into the abyss purgatory
surrounded by all your old "fellows"
Let's see how we welcome you
Being stuck in Loong Palace...
How could you avenge your son?
Even I feel nervous for you
You fools are in no place to gloat
I was simply trying to help
But it seems that you
don't appreciate it
You must've forgotten
what I'm capable of
Ah! I know this one
The Sky... Sky... Sky...
Sky-Splitting Claw
Thank you
Master Shen can take this claw
to Chentang Pass
and use it to tear open a rift
leading back to me
The Abyss Monsters can then
help you destroy your enemy
The Abyss Monsters?
How... is that possible?
They were trapped
by the Suppression Seal
for a thousand years
How could they possibly escape?
The Loongs...
have they already released them?
With the Sea-Stabilizing Chains
binding us
there's no chance for escape
This is a win-win tactic
What do you say, my brother?
You wouldn't be so generous
Get to the point
What's your price?
In this purgatory
where flames burn our bodies
every day feels like a year
If you could
slightly lower the lava's heat
easing our suffering
we'd be willing to serve you
with all our might
What's going on?
What is Shen Gongbao up to now?
Finally, we're out! Yay!
Bye-bye!
Vile
We're doomed
How will we explain this
to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us
- Here
- What for?
I'll break your arms
and then you break my legs
We'll say the Yaksha did it
Oh! When the general sees
how badly we're hurt
he won't blame us anymore
Try your best
Hit harder!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, you two!
Master Immortal, you're here!
He let the Yaksha get away!
Huh? It was all your fault
Who are you to point fingers?
Who are you to play innocent?
Oh my
Dumb and Dumber!
Hey!
You two boneheads!
Get over here and guard me!
- Yes, Sir!
- Right away!
Show no mercy
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead
Chentang Pass and the Loongs have
no reason to fight
Taiyi is rebuilding
Ao Bing's body right now
Liar!
The shield...
No!
Master! Master!
Ao Bing!
Master Taiyi has built me a new body
Please, ceasefire
Shen Gongbao
I saved your disciple
How will you thank me?
So... that's Nezha in there?
Why, you ungrateful jerk!
- Master!
- They must die!
Ha ha ha!
You think you can break this shield?
Hit me! Come on!
No!
The aura...
Ao Bing!
Father!
I failed the mission
to save our kind
No. None of that matters
I just want you to be safe
As long as you're here
it's enough for me
Open Lotus!
Your body, what is...
Please, he's literally a newborn
How could he take a hit like that?
Ao Bing!
Hey! It's not ready yet!
Don't move! Don't move!
Ao Bing, what's going on?
Don't move before your body is fixed
If your body exceeds its limit
it will collapse!
For heaven's sake...
Fatty!
Make another bod...
body for Ao Bing now!
Making two bodies back-to-back
has completely drained
the Sacred Lotus's energy
Without a body,
won't his soul scatter?
Master, do something!
Without the Sacred Lotus
there's nothing I can do
It's okay
I took your place
as the Spirit Pearl, I deserve this
If my sacrifice
can bring you back to life
then it's a fair price to pay
Who asked you to?
I am happy being the Demon Orb
Don't you dare die!
Father
please spare Chentang Pass
We should stop our mistakes
This is my final wish
There has to be other ways
There has to
You! Try harder!
Let Ao Bing share your body for now
Share your body
Two souls sharing one body
rejection is inevitable
The Spirit Pearl and Demon Orb come
from the same source
Sharing one body
for seven days
shouldn't be a problem
That's it!
Ao Bing, come on up! Quick!
Okay
This feels... strange...
Ao Bing, are you here?
Yes, I am
I can hear your voice in my head!
This is fun!
But this is only a temporary fix
What happens after seven days?
There's some potion
in the vault of Yu Xu Palace
Elixir Reparo
It can restore the divine power
of magical items
With it
the Sacred Lotus will bloom again
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go to the Supreme Lord himself
and beg for it
Or are you planning to
report on me and the Loongs?
The Supreme Lord wouldn't sa...
save a son of the Loongs
If asking doesn't work
then we'll snatch
Yu Xu Palace is
at the core of the Chan Sect
protected by formidable powers
For my son
I'll break into the Court of Heaven
if I have to
Your Majesty, calm down
I might have a plan
Chan disciples
who excel in their training
can participate
in the Ascension Trial
Passing the trial grants
not only immortality
but also the right to choose one
ma... magic item
from the Yu Xu Vault as a reward
Are you suggesting
that Nezha participate in the trial
to obtain the elixir?
No, no, no!
He's beaming with demonic energy!
As soon as he uses his powers,
he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing already sharing
Nezha's body?
His divine aura can mask
the demonic energy perfectly
As long as he passes the trial
within seven days
not only will we
have the el... elixir...
But he can also
achieve immortality!
Does that mean I won't be
a demon anymore?
This will save
both Ao Bing and Nezha
Eve... everyone is happy
This isn't the right thing to do
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules
Come clean with the Supreme Lord
and trust his judgement
My wife and I will
also plead for mercy
so the sins of the parents
don't affect the children
Mere mortals
you have only decades
of life experience
how dare you lecture me
about morality?
Longer than I could remember
I've lived for thousands of years
Let me tell you one truth
and one truth only
If my son die
I'll have Chentang Pass
sink with him
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend
I will save him for sure
But if you dare
to harm Chentang Pass
I'll smash your Loong Palace
into P-I-E-C-E-S!
Except for Nezha and Taiyi
no one leaves Chentang Pass
from now on
If in seven days
I don't see Elixir Reparo
or the news of my clan gets out
I'll let Chentang Pass
sink forever
I don't trust my siblings
and I can't stay
out of my body for long
The fate of Chentang Pass
is in your hands
Yes
Exactly
There's no message
that can't be conveyed
with just a nod
Lord Li
we're all here to say goodbye
to Young Master Nezha
We want to thank him
for saving the entire city
You're too kind
My son has caused enough troubles
over the years
I always knew the Young Master
was destined for greatness
Look at him
a wide forehead
broad face
prominent nose
full cheeks and thick lips
All signs of a true hero!
I've never been wrong
in reading faces
Young Master, remember to brush
your teeth after meals!
Boss
the Demon Slayers is now rebranded
as the Nezha Gang
All members will follow your orders
Young Master,
want to practice calligraphy?
I'm here for you!
Young Master,
you're three years old now
It's time to get a girlfriend
Any interests in instrument?
We're proficient in all of them
I want to
play shuttlecock
What?
It's fun
Anyone?
I'll play with you
Didn't you always want to play
shuttlecock with me?
Well...
he's a bit hard on the kicks
I'm a general of war!
Dad
That's my boy!
How about...
we play it another day?
Nonsense!
Why stop when you're having fun?
It's fine. I'm fine
I'll join too!
My lady, you don't have to do this
Are you looking down on me?
I'm also a general of war!
Nezha, catch this!
Kiddo
how did you miss that?
If only I weren't the Demon Orb...
What was that?
Nothing
It's time to go
Before you go
will you give your mother
a big hug?
Please, people are watching
Wait
Here are some snacks I made
For you and your master on the road
Okay, okay
We need to go
Hey! I'm not on board yet!
Your body isn't fully fixed
Don't use too much force
Alright, alright
And watch your temper
Try to stay calm out there
Without me and your father
by your side
learn to take care of yourself
You silly child
What's wrong with just a hug?
That's too much
It's not a farewell anyway
Let's move
Why are you sighing?
Taste bad?
Food, food, food
All you know is food
Look at me
I'm too worried to even eat!
Have you thought
about how to pass the trial?
What is the trial about?
It'll test the progress
of your cultivation
In front of the judges
you must defeat, barehanded three
demon kings of earth-monster level
Fighting...
That's my specialty!
But as soon as you
give off demonic energy
your identity will be exposed
Just let Ao Bing control my body
His divine energy
will be just as powerful
Sounds easy
Let's try
Nezha, fully relax your body
Let Ao Bing take control
and fight me
Ao Bing, what are you doing?
Keep steady!
When a soul inhabits another body
unless your willpower is
much stronger than the host's
you won't be able
to fully control it
Nezha, step back
The harder you push
the less Ao Bing can control
Use your leg!
Sweep him, sweep him!
Don't panic! I'm coming...
for you
Having fun, huh?
We're almost at Yu Xu Palace
and you're still messing around
Look at yourself
what kind of mentor are you?
Stand here
and reflect on your mistakes
No meals until you figure it out!
You're a grown man
Stop acting like a reckless teenager
I got it!
The Sleepy-Slumber Pill
What's that?
Take this,
and you'll fall asleep immediately
Once you're asleep
Ao Bing can fully control your body
Brilliant!
One is enough
Should've told me...earlier
Perfect
Master Taiyi?
Now this feels like the real deal
What's wrong?
Don't worry
I see you've completely
taken over Nezha's body
Let's go again
This time, I won't hold back
You'd better give it your all, too
I humbly seek your guidance
Not bad
Barely able to match my skills
Master Taiyi, your nose is bleeding
Too heaty recently
Need more water
No big deal
Kunlun Mountain! We're here
I heard a day here
equals a year in the mortal world
Don't worry,
we're not in the celestial realm yet
But this many people?
They've all come to seek immortality
Chan Sect is famous across the world
and everyone wants to join
Look at this. The jasper
It's the credential
of a Chan Sect immortal
With it
you'll receive respect
everywhere you go, I'm telling ya
Being an immortal is amazing
Both of your brothers have ascended
You'll have no problem either
I mean Nezha's brothers
His two brothers
are among the best
of the third-generation disciples
You know
how Nezha always misbehaves, right?
So, I often tell stories
about his brothers
to set a good example for him
Let me tell you something
Nezha idolizes his brothers
Oh wow, you're lucky...
to meet the well-known Demon Hunters
Demon Hunters?
They roam the land, hunting down
demons that wreak havoc on humanity
keeping the world at peace
The current leader
of the Demon Hunters
is the top disciple
of Immortal Wuliang
Isn't his predecessor Shen Gongbao?
Master Taiyi
what's that smoke over there?
Oh, that's the most
precious treasure of Yu Xu Palace
The Tianyuan Cauldron
Brother Taiyi
it's been forever
Brother Wuliang!
I heard that
during Master's seclusion
you've been in charge
of Yu Xu Palace
I've brought my disciple to
participate in the Ascension Trial
Nezha, come meet Master Wuliang
Master Wuliang
So, you're Nezha?
The reincarnation
of the Spirit Pearl?
Oh my!
How remarkable!
The Supreme Lord holds
great expectations for you
And you sure don't disappoint
Look at him
so full of robust vitality
giving off a righteous vibe
The boy's been over training lately
His state is a bit unstable
What do you think you're doing?
This is Yu Xu Palace!
I need to pee
- Crana!
- Here!
Take the child to the restroom
Restroom?
I didn't say anything about resting
Idiot!
Restroom
is where you pee
The boy's a bit rough
Please forgive him
Wow! So white!
Is the entire palace made of jade?
Where did they get
so much money to buy jade?
The "Yu" in Yu Xu Palace
means jade, right?
Then what does the "Xu" mean?
Humble?
Guilty? Or emptiness?
Is the restroom also made of jade?
Even immortals need to pee?
Does Master Wuliang also... poop?
This is a place of seclusion
Lower your voice
How much further is the restroom?
I can't hold it anymore!
Hey, sister, wait for me!
You...
I didn't mean it
I need to change my skirt
Go by yourself
But I don't know
where the restroom is
Go through the corridor,
turn right, then left
Oh
Wow! How fancy it is!
Radical!
Emm... Am I lost?
Where are you going?
Oh, I got lost
Follow me
Brother, good job
on raising the Spirit Pearl
Another great achievement
for the Sect
Not at all
It's all thanks to Master's guidance
This Kunlun Dew is a rare elixir
Normally, it takes six months
to fill a basin
But today,
when I sent someone to check
it's already full!
Your timing couldn't be better
Brother
luck sure favors you, doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
Can't even drink water properly
My disciple is a bit crude
Please forgive him
My pee is in the water
My master is a bit crude, too
Please forgive him
Brother
time is of the essence
I think Nezha should go
through the trial immediately
Why the rush?
Let's have a few more drinks first
No more, please
Alright then
My disciple Deero will be the judge
The next target of Demon Hunters
could go to Nezha
Brother, excuse us
Taiyi, my brother
is always so impatient
The taste of the Dew this year
is especially rich
Keep using this method in the future
Yes, master
Why stop?
It's been six hours, Master Shen
We're too tired to continue
Rubbish!
Cultivation allows no laziness
Without my permission
you're not allowed to stop
General Li Jing of Chentang Pass
is here to see you
Master Shen
yesterday's battle
left many soldiers and civilians
of Chentang Pass injured
We've run out of medicine
I humbly ask you to open a path
so that a few doctors can leave
the city to buy supplies
How bold!
No wonder you're...
Who did that?
You son of a...
I...
St... stop, stop, stop!
Bring me the one
you've caught earlier
He escaped the city
during the battle
General Li, please
take him ba... back with you
This is a misunderstanding,
Master Shen!
I'm a demon too!
I captured this Yaksha
to clear my son's name
Now that it's settled
and since he hasn't done
anything worse
just let him go
Yes, exactly
I'm just a small role
Insignificant
I don't think you understood me
No one leaves here, not even a demon
Let alone humans
Master Shen, please have mercy
I'm a demon, too
We are both villains!
Pfft! I'm n... not a villain
Everyone who knows the secret
of the Spirit Pearl
must stay here
Without medicine
the injured won't survive
Master Shen, please
I'm only asking to save lives
Sir!
We caught a spy
This man came from outside the city
and he injured some of our soldiers
Lock... lock him up too
Brother
Brother, is that you?
You...
Brother, it's me!
Xiaobao?
You haven't been home for centuries
I miss you so much
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to find you
Look
the compass you gave me
It tells me where you are
Father... how is he doing?
He's great
Ever since you entered Yu Xu Palace
father's been full of energy
like he took some miracle tonic
You are the only one
from our village ever
made it as a Chan Sect immortal
Now, fellow demons from miles around
are pouring in to train with father
By the way
why are you here?
Didn't you promise me before
that once I've achieved human form
you'd get me into Yu Xu Palace?
Look! I can turn into a human now!
All these years,
I've trained so hard
never rested a day
You're my role model, big brother
Glory to Yu Xu,
answering heaven's call
Travel the world,
bringing justice to all
Say, brother
what are you doing here?
I... I...
Are these sea monsters
your subordinates?
Why are you
surrounding Chentang Pass?
Well, about that...
Th...this is...
Master Shen is
defending Chentang Pass
Huh?
Evil forces invaded the city
Master Shen and the sea clan
came to our aid
On behalf of my people,
I thank you for this noble act
Don't mention it
Brother, you're incredible!
Is this the demon
attacking Chentang Pass?
Ah!
You are a disgrace to all demons!
Shame on you!
Hey, Xiaobao
can you wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
Huh?Why?
I can transform into a human now!
It's just that...
I'm preparing for my promotion
to the Twelve Golden Immortals
so I can't be distracted
Twelve Golden Immortals?
Once it's done
I'll take you there
okay?
No problem, brother!
Your promotion is more important
I can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime
Besides
I haven't quite mastered
the shape-shifting
I'll go back and practice more
Practice more
Xiaobao
this is what I've saved up
since I entered the palace
What is it?
Yu Xu Palace gives all disciples
these immortality pills
Take one and you ga...
gain ten years' worth of cultivation
But... this is too precious
Brother, you're training
for a promotion
You should keep them
I don't like how it tastes
I prefer cultivating on my own
You... you should bring them back
Share them with the family
No, I can't. Father will blame me
Xiaobao, are you not
obeying your big brother?
Take the pills and leave now
This is the front line
If... if you stay
I'll be distracted
Then... I...
I'll leave
Brother
You must make it
into the Twelve Golden Immortals
I'll keep on training too
I appreciate your help
but the stake is too high
for me to let anyone through
This Yaksha...
you... you bring him back, too
I wasn't helping you
I was helping the young one
A good role model
can change his life
Wait
Le... leave me a list
of medicines you need
I am Nezha, the Third Prince bold
I slay the demons,
I write in rhyme untold
Today I come
to rid the evil's breath
You wicked fiends,
prepare for death!
Still eating?
You are doomed
Ahhh!
Who do you think you are?
Barging into our Bandits Hill?
So, you're in charge?
Come forward
and have a taste of my power
You arrogant spoilt brat
Boss, teach him a lesson
Show me what you got
You go
No, but, boss...
how dare I steal your thunder?
Fighting a child is
just embarrassing
When I say go, you go
Hey, kid
Too young, too naive
So, I'm willing to let this slide
You, you...
It's still not too late
to run home to mommy
What's wrong?
- Why are you awake again?
- I don't know
I'm a light sleeper
All that shaking has jolted me awake
Darn it
He took too much of that pills
and now he's immune
Increase the dose then
If you insist to stay
you might get hurt
I was going to dodge to the right
Sorry, I thought it was left
So weak
Master Taiyi
Maybe I should cut in
He could use
a few more years' training
Not so fast
He was just teasing the demon
The boy likes to...
play dumb
Pills... I need pills
I gave you a warning
Now you know who you're messing with
Oh no! The pills have
dissolved in the soup!
Then I'll drink the soup
And you're trying to steal our soup?
This calls for a beating
Let me
So gross
Super Mighty Club Strike!
See?
I told you he was pretending
I wasn't paying attention
That didn't count
Not possible!
You suck!
Step aside!
Watch me kick his butt
Why did you spit it all out?
The taste is too strong
I couldn't help it
Check this out!
Funny!
This isn't working
We can't win without the pill
Deero is watching
I can't give you the pill
What do we do now?
I got it
There is another way
You're not suggesting...
We can eat the puke
But... it's disgusting
What's the big deal?
Remember when I drank Yaksha booger?
This explains a lot
No pain
No gain
That's how Nezha defeat fate
Lives of my parents
and friends are at stake
and the people of Chentang Pass
E-A-S-Y P-E-A-S-Y!
By ignoring prejudice
and overcoming inner fears
I will change my destiny
I kept low-key
until today's show
Master Taiyi
Save Nezha first
Then we'll figure out
a way for Elixir Reparo
No way
I don't believe this
Kid, let's fight another round
Playing dead?
I'll smash you!
Good thing Nezha got knocked out
You do suck!
Let me avenge you!
Invincible Whirlwind Punch!
Ahhh!
Do we have to catch them all?
Even leaving one behind
could harm the people here
Take them all back to Yu Xu Palace
The Sect will guide them
to the right path
turning evil to good
What's with the face?
No biggy
His look switches from time to time
Spirit Pearl, you know
not like normal people
Be more careful next time
You scared the life out of me
Who's this kid?
Nezha, possibly
Younger brother of Jinzha and Muzha
He's the Spirit Pearl reincarnation
appointed by the Supreme Lord
Not likely, huh?
Hunched back
Wobbly pace
Sinking brows and drooping eyes
Disgusting face
Not to mention the dark eye circles
Looks more like a ghost
Not now
Brother
what's the star sign tonight?
Six stars in alignment
once in a decade
Whenever six stars align
this Jade Podium can transmit sound
and images across thousands of miles
Our brothers scatter
all over the world
can finally get together
Tonight is the night
the Golden Immortals shall meet
I haven't ascended to the Twelve yet
Maybe I shouldn't be included
It's only a matter of time
No...
It's not appropriate at all
I can't do it, really
Then why are you sitting up there?
Shut up!
Would it kill you
to see your master thrive?
A Sauna!
Shh!
Brothers and sisters, I humbly
welcome you back to your places
Greetings, Brother Wuliang!
Allow me to introduce a new member
Brother Taiyi
He has fulfilled
the master's expectations
and successfully nurtured
the Spirit Pearl reincarnation
Pay your respect
The Deification War is imminent
We are here
to discuss the preparation
Chan Sect is the orthodox of Tao
so we're destined to win
But as Jie Sect has
risen rapidly these years
we must remain vigilant
Jie Sect
is where furry
and horned beasts gather
and creatures born of mucus and eggs
This war concerns
the survival of our sect
We must be careful
Strengthening our power
is the key
Precisely
That's why I began preparing early
Immortality pills
a total of nine thousands
could be allocated
according to grades
This will definitely
boost our strength
How could there be so many?
For a hundred years
our master has tirelessly refined
pills with the Tianyuan Cauldron
working day and night
at the cost of his own cultivation
Brother Wuliang has dedicated
himself to building our sect
his contributions are to be praised
Aye, aye
Besides the Jie Sect
are there other evil forces
plotting against us?
Master Cihang
as soon as menacing demons
are discovered
The Demon Hunters will be
immediately sent out
So, most stray demons pose no threat
But there is one exception
Oh? Who is that?
The Eastern Sea Loongs
Loongs?
Didn't they surrender
to the Court of Heaven long ago?
No kind could be trusted
except for our own
To me
Their surrender is merely a facade
hibernating for the moment
The Loongs have helped
subdue the abyss monsters
for thousands of years
What's their crime?
But they own great strength
If they betray us in the war
the whole situation
could be overturned
But we still can't do that
Our reputation of righteous
and just is known to all
If we gratuitously
attack the surrendered
how will anyone ever trust us?
Aye
- We must not act rashly
- Further deliberation is necessary
- But...
- Enough
They made their points
And you don't have to be bigoted
OK
The time of the six-star alignment
is almost over
Since there are no other topics
let's adjourn the meeting
Brother
Jinzha and Muzha
are disciples of myself
and Brother Puxian
They have been cultivating here
for many years away from home
and have never even met Nezha
their younger brother
Since there's still time left
in the six-star alignment
why not let them
meet for a while?
Great idea
OMG!
What should I do?
What?
Speaking of my look...
Will my first impression...
Be bad?
Of course not!
Really?
Though slovenly
you've got strong will
Though short
you've got a big heart
Though ugly
you're kind inside
Though you have dark eye circles
piggy nose
and a missing tooth
I still think
you're truly incredibly great
And I'm sure
your brothers would agree
Thanks for the compliment
What are you doing?
You go meet my brothers for me
Seriously?
How can I do this for you?
No, Nezha
Nezha!
The boy is a bit shy
Brother!
Ao Bing
you cried?
This reminded me of my two brothers
You have brothers too?
Mm. I used to
Having two such wonderful brothers
You're so lucky
What were you talking
about just now?
They said
they're sorry for not
checking on you all these years
They asked
how things have been at home
if your parents are well
what hobbies you have
and who your friends are
They also said
that whatever problems
you may have in the future
go to them
And remember, you have two brothers
who will always help and protect you
Why are you...
Nothing.
It's just sand in my eyes
You sure
it's not the other way around?
Shut up! I said it's nothing
OK. You are the boss here
I'm not talking to you
Fine
I'll stop
Are you still mad? Nezha?
Nezha!
Ao Bing
I've been violent and unruly
since I was young
making my parents worry all day
Your father
though he attacked Chentang Pass
I know he only risk everything
for your sake
And today
my brothers were so kind to me
Our families have
sacrificed so much for us
You're a monster
and I'm a demon
We're both burdens for our families
So what if we were born as demons?
Immortal or demon, I make the choice
Once you are saved
we must win ourselves
a place among the immortals
so our families won't
have to worry anymore
Yes!
Only by becoming immortals
can we have everyone's respect
Deal!
I'm going to become an immortal!
Only with courage and diligence can
great progress be made
At this speed
hundred years would still be in vain
About cultivating
The priorities are vitality,
energy, and spirit
If you feel it's hard
or exhausting
that's because you were born demons
Only by giving it all
You'll have a chance
to change your destiny
and achieve immortality
Life or death, of none I'm scared
defying authority is
what I've revered
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan
This bad boy will
become a godly man!
Bravo!
Just a few lines, yet so powerful
truly inspiring
A great poem, indeed
This is something
all of you should learn from
Really? Is it that good?
I just made it up
It is good
Every word counts
and encouraging
A poem like this
shows the ambition of you, young man
A true young hero
with a bright future ahead!
Oh, come on. It's just fine
Actually,
it still has some tiny flaws
More like plenty of flaws
Let me ask you
what's with those dark eye circles?
It's obvious
you stay up late all the time
Your life is undisciplined
your diet unhealthy
and you can't even manage
basic self-control
How dare you dream
of becoming an immortal?
I was born with dark eye circles
Appearance reflects the heart,
don't you know?
Take a look at yourself
in the mirror
Ridiculous
reckless and sloppy
If you were my disciple
I'd make you rebuild your human form
It can be rebuilt?
Then there's hope
for my looks, right?
Teach me, please
I knew you came
to find yourself a master
Listen, kid
I see you have great ambition
so I'll take you as my disciple
Cool! Master!
Come train with your brothers
- Train for what?
- Immortality, of course
I don't need you to teach me that
Show me how to be prettier
Ridiculous!
You're putting looks
before cultivation?
Get your priorities straight
Are you teaching me or not?
We're no longer master and disciple
You deserve to have
panda eyes for life
That's too much
I was going to go easy on you!
What is this?
Are you challenging me?
Three pills should be enough
Kid, go back where you came from
If you keep disrupting our class
this could end badly for you
Apologies
You're no match for me
Impressive, kid
I underestimated you
Try this!
Yeah, teach this ignorant brat
a lesson
Master will surely win!
So fast!
You saw it?
We have no grudges between us
You'd better go
I cannot lose
You can't even touch me
Let alone fight
Smart move!
Hold him tight
Speedy is junky
Surrender?
Wait, you are...
You've finally figured it out
I'm not fast
I just transform
into electric currents
traveling instantly to any location
In water
I am invincible!
Impressive cryo power
Stay calm
Try too hard
and your body will collapse!
Ice doesn't conduct electricity
Let's see what else you've got
Lakes and seas...
Clouds and sky...
By this divine talisman in my hand
Wind is to rise and rain is to fall
Swift and Uplift!
Father!
Darn it
The Rain Summoning Spell
End this now!
Too late
You're doomed
Master!
Master, are you all right?
I wasn't going to take your life
You didn't have to sacrifice an arm
All disciples, listen
take the demons back to the palace
Yes!
Stop!
Put them down
All of you, put them down!
May I ask if you are a member
of the Chan Sect?
That's correct
These are all immortals
from Yu Xu Palace
You must not be disrespectful
Entering Yu Xu Palace
and receiving the teachings
of the righteous path
may not be a bad thing
All of you, drop your weapons!
Father!
Xiaobao?
How come you're back?
Xiaobao, stand down!
Xiaobao!
Demon!
How dare you!
No!
Father!
Nezha, freeze the river now!
You can't escape!
Father!
Go!
Go now!
Run!
Father...
There's no escape
Step aside
He's just trying to save his father
You didn't have to be so brutal
Panax notoginseng
cattail pollen
munjeet
borneol
Loong's blood
- One more basket
- Safflower
angelica
pseudo-ginseng powder
sappanwood
poison nut
My lord
we now have everything on the list
along with a hundred baskets
of sea products
We happen to be short
on food supplies
Master Shen, a moment, please
We've prepared a meal
Would you honor us
with your presence?
You...
Thanks to Lord Li's kindness
I've been taken in as a servant
He may be a demon
but he has a good heart
As long as he behaves
there's no reason
he can't have a future
I wonder if the dishes
suit your taste
Not...
Not bad
Then have some more
Try this liquor as well
I quit long ago
Cultivators must sup...
suppress desires
As the saying goes
one must cut off urges
to perfect the spirit
Another saying goes
one must practice kindness
to polish virtue
Talking won't help
I've already re...
reached the point of no return
You can't hide forever
The truth will come out one day
If you continue to harm lives
and make more mistakes
even if you can deceive everyone
you won't be able to fool yourself
And you will not improve
further on your cultivation
the essence of which
is doing good deeds
- and walking the righteous path
- Enough!
What nonsense!
You know nothing about cultivation
Sir!
Someone is here to see Master Shen
Brother
Who did this to you?
Some Taoists
They attacked
Father...
had one of his arms
cut off
Who did it?
His name is...
Ne... Zha
Congratulations on passing Level 2
Please inform Brother Wuliang
Master is in seclusion
refining pills
and has not emerged yet
Before Level 3
why don't you rest for a few days?
We only have two days left
No need
I'm fine
Let's continue the test
Well, as you wish
The final test
is the demon Queen of Skull Mountain
Shi Ji
Someone is requesting an urgent
meeting with Master Taiyi
Please help us!
It's Chentang Pass
Something happened!
Dad
Mom
Dad?
Mom?
Dad!
Mom!
Calm down
Let's keep looking
Keep looking
I received an urgent report as soon
as I ended seclusion
Who could have committed
such a horrendous crime?
Master
according to Shieldos
they were struck
by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness
When they woke up
people of Chentang Pass had
already been slaughtered
We haven't obtained the elixir yet
Why would they do that?
Brother
any clue?
No, no
I was just thinking
where did all this lava come from?
Exactly
There are no volcanoes
for hundreds of miles around
This is truly bizarre
Everyone, come quick!
What demon is this?
This is...
left by a Loong's claw
Impossible!
The Loongs are all in Eastern Sea
guarding the Suppression Seal
Not a single one could have left
Master, if I remember correctly
Queen Ao Run of Western Sea
has a special skill
called the Sky...
Sky-Splitting Claw
Are you saying
she used the Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That explains the lava
It must have been transported
from the purgatory remotely
But she's watched
by the Loong King of Eastern Sea
It's impossible
for her to cross over
Then there's only
one possibility left
The thing I worried the most
happened
The King of Eastern Sea
has betrayed us?
This is too serious an accusation
Could we be wrong?
No
It's them!
What are you doing?
Don't be impulsive
Are you heading to the Loong Palace?
That's the direction
of Skull Mountain
The Loongs slaughtered
innocent civilians
committing this
unforgivable atrocity
No need to consult
with fellow Golden Immortals
I'll strike first and explain later
Crana, back to the palace with me
Summon all the Demon Hunters
Roger
Brother
Nezha's parents were
killed by demons
We can't let anything
happen to the child
Go with Deero for him now
Yes
I know you're heartbroken right now
but can you please
calm down for a moment?
Can you take me
to the Loong Palace first?
I'll confront my father and master
to get to the bottom of this
Will that bring my parents back?
Mirror mirror on the wall
who's the fairest
within ten miles and more?
It's you, my lady
And who is the fairest
within a hundred miles?
It's you, my lady
What about a thousand miles?
- It's you
- And ten thousand miles?
- And in the whole world?
Still you
Do you think I'm stupid?
Lie better, at least
No, no
I was just trying
not to piss you off
You know what?
Telling the truth won't make me mad
Seriously?
I, Lady Shi Ji,
am indeed a stunning beauty
but I know
there's always someone better
Go on and ask then
Am I the fairest of them all?
No
Fair enough
Am I the fairest
- within ten thousand miles?
- No
- What about a thousand miles?
- What about a hundred miles?
- No
Ten miles?
Nope
Am I even the fairest
on this mountain?
Nope
Screw you!
There isn't any other female
in this mountain
I'm female, too
You promised you won't get mad
- You are prettier than me?
- Help!
How the hell!
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji
Darn kid
Have we even met?
What the hell are you up to?
You will be exposed
Let me
Stay out of it
You think you can defeat me?
The entire mountain is my body
I'll see how you can destroy me
If you use more force
your body will collapse!
I said
stay out of it!
It has already started!
Crap!
I'm so screwed
Luckily there's some left
I shall live to fight another day
Darn kid
Just you wait
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
No escape!
Oh my! Reckless child
You body has almost gone
Are you trying to kill yourself?
What's that fire earlier?
Isn't Nezha
a frost mage?
Who... who said that?
Frost, flame,
I taught him everything
His powers are
a combination of ice and fire
Is that possible?
The Spirit Pearl is endowed
with unparalleled talents
Can't judge him by normal standards
Which one of us is the teacher?
You think you know better than me?
I wouldn't dare
However
I did sense a strong presence
of demonic energy earlier
About that...
Shi Ji must have released it
What are you saying, fatty?
I did not...
Was it you? Just tell me, was it?
Say it!
Yes, it was me
Stop shaking
I'm about to throw up!
See? I told you
Nezha
you've passed three levels
Today
I will personally cast
the Ascension Spell for you
I've been through
all of this back then
I was probably too nervous
The Ascension Spell is longer
than I remember
From now on
you're an Immortal of the Chan Sect
This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
houses all sorts of rare magic items
Elixir Reparo
You can only pick one
Don't you need more time?
Elixir Reparo
Yu Xu Palace has sent messengers
to inform the Twelve about
what the Loongs did
However, due to the great distance
my brothers and sisters can't
make it here sooner
This time
I myself will lead the hunt
on the Loongs
Nezha
will you fight alongside me?
Let me go back
to Chentang Pass first
Then we'll seek revenge
on the Loong King
OK
With your extraordinary
combat skills
you'd be a great help
in destroying the Loong Palace
I've paid back
everything I owed you
Wait
When I get my body back
I will go with you
to the Loong Palace, okay?
You know well what I'm going to do
You being there
will only make it harder
Next time we meet
we're foes instead of friends
Karma it is
No, you can't leave!
Your soul will scatter
before you get to the Loong Palace
Nine-Loong Fire Trap!
Calm down, will you?
Going now won't change anything
Leave me alone
Let me out!
No!
I promised Nezha
I'd save you no matter what
Suffocating!
Who's there?
I'm Immortal Wuliang
of the Chan Sect
Ao Guang, do you admit your guilt?
So you've found out?
Is Ao Bing still alive?
I'll accept
whatever punishment you give me
but please spare my son
Nonsense!
The Court of Heaven
ordered your clan
to suppress the sea monsters
Instead, you colluded with them
and slaughtered Chentang Pass
What?
The Loongs have committed
an unforgivable crime
Today justice shall be served
Encompassed are
the earth and the skies
Unleash the power
with boundless might
Let the Tianyuan rise and stand tall
Reign supreme above them all
Open Cauldron!
Show yourselves!
What have you done to Chentang Pass?
Didn't big brother tell us
to follow Master Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Speaking of the emergency
you should focus on present
My King
we can't sit here and wait to die!
If I go into battle
the Suppression Seal will...
Leave that to us
Joining all our powers
we can hold it for long enough
Fine
I've had enough!
You wretched demon!
This is an once-in-a-millennium
chance for revenge
Break out of the purgatory!
Destroy the Loong Palace!
Soul Blade!
Old fool! Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic energy
like this...
aren't you afraid
of exposing your identity?
I told you
if you dared to harm Chentang Pass
I would smash your palace
into PIECES!
Tell me!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Move! Out of my way!
Rise!
Do you have a death wish?
Let's see how long
your body can take it
I don't care if I live or die
As long as you're dead!
Now is the time!
Look what you've done!
Is annihilation
for all really what you want?
The chains
Even the Eastern Sea Loong King
can't match your power
I was right after all
You're exactly
what the Chan Sect needs
Your parents spent
their lives fighting evil
From now on
you must carry on their legacy
and eliminate all the demons
Let me avenge your loss
by turning these jerks into pills
Escort me!
Yes, master!
Nezha!
Dad!
Mom!
Nezha!
Son, are you alright?
Your body...
I... I...
They already know
about you and Ao Bing
I... I... I thought...
I'd never see you again
Master is still casting the spell
We need to buy
as much time as we can
Nezha, it wasn't my father
who slaughtered Chentang Pass
The real culprit
is him, the Immortal Wuliang!
Shieldos!
Loongs
Brother
it's been a while
Why are you here?
Shen Gongbao
you collude with the Loongs
What are you up to?
I should be ask... asking you
You captured my father
What are you up to?
Who said I captured your father?
Only you know my family's situation
If you didn't give the order
why would Nezha and the Demon
Hunters hunt my father down?
And my little brother's
arrow wound...
It's obviously
caused by your disciple, Deero!
There's the talent
I recruited myself
Nothing slips past you
After all, I've done your dirty work
for so many years
I can also guess your purpose here
putting up a show in Chentang Pass
You are trying to fram...
frame the Loongs, aren't you?
Is this how you repay me,
your brother and mentor?
You've always use...
used me for your benefit
Between you and me
there's only grudge, not gratitude
May I interest you in a deal?
Master Immortal
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace
you must know the spell to unhinge
the Sea-Stabilizing Chains
I do. So what?
You... you are going to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us
fought the celestial realm together
Who betrayed us and
cast us into the purgatory?
Now Wuliang is targeting Ao Guang
that's exactly what we want
I've long heard that
Immortal Wuliang
recruit talents without bias
I trust it you know well
what we can do
If you can free us
from the purgatory
and help us achieve immortality
we are willing to offer
our humble service
Plus the secret of the Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb
The Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb?
Pathetic!
Whe... where's your spirit
of fighting back?
We were young and ignorant!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
and the rulers
Smart
But you're so unpredictable
How can I trust you?
Unless you let me place on you...
We are willing
The three Loongs willingly agreed
to let Wuliang place a curse on them
If they dare
to disobey in the future
Wuliang can take their lives
at any time
Wuliang then fulfilled his promise
freeing them
from the Sea-Stabilizing Chains
Whenever a powerful force
is discovered
he orchestrates massacres
frames others
and sends troops to capture them
According to Shen Gongbao
he had carried out many
such tasks for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance
to join the Chan Sect
This time, Wuliang came
to destroy Chentang Pass
and frame the Loongs of Eastern Sea
One thing led to another
he ended up recruiting
the three Loong kings
And from them
he learned the secret of
the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl
After that
they deliberately left
two clueless survivors
to tell Yu Xu Palace
what had happened
Seeing no hope of breaking through
Shen Gongbao came up with a plan
He had the Yaksha petrify us
then hide us in the sewers
Later, he waited
for the right time to revive us
And you?
My families are gone
I have nothing left to hold onto
Over there!
The demons captured
by the Demon Hunters
are not, as outsiders think
being reformed in Yu Xu Palace
Instead, they are thrown into
the Tianyuan Cauldron by Wuliang
refined into pills of immortality
to strengthen the Chan Sect's power
Brother
how could you
commit such atrocities?
How... How are you
going to face our master
and the teachings we received?
Now that you know what Wuliang did
you should stop before it's too late
Take him back to the palace
to face punishment
from the Supreme Lord
The Demon Hunters were
personally trained by Master Wuliang
Do you think a few words
would turn us against him?
So
I was wrong about the Loongs
Let them go!
Let me help
You betrayed us?
We learned that from you,
Big Brother
Back then,
in order to protect our kind
I had no choice!
Well, in order to protect myself now
Neither do I
My King, wait for us!
Don't leave us behind!
My King, take us with you!
My King! My King!
You've all been sold out!
Loong King of Southern Sea
Loong King of Northern Sea
Loong Queen of Western Sea
Nephew
it's playtime with your uncle
Take my spear!
Take my axe!
Take my wheel!
Take my wheel times a hundred!
Two hundreds!
Three hundreds!
Enough, huh?
Bullshit!
There weren't that many
Your body is still unstable
Don't exhaust yourself
For my mistakes
I would give my life
for freeing the Loongs
Young and vicious
Let me have some fun with you,
little one
Bullying a child
shameless and vile!
Hey! How dare you
hit your master's brother!
Bullying an uncle eat a knuckle!
This won't do. This is a mess
Then let's make it
an even bigger one
How about some vapor?
Sure
Take them down!
Watch out for sneak attacks!
There you are
Careful, it's me!
Brother?
My apologies
Nezha!
Surprise!
Transformation Spell?
Are you insane?
You can't fool me
What are you...
Code.
She sells seashells by the seashore
What?
You don't know the code
Imposter!
So you really are an imposter!
Unbelievable!
Serves you right
Code
Eh... he sells bells
in the big well?
Wrong!
It's "she sells seashells
by the seashore"
"and the shells she sells
all smell for sure"
I'm the real one!
How come I don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can you make it easier?
It's too hard!
You idiot!
Don't come near me! Imposter!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
Crap! You don't know the code!
Neither do you!
That's true
Does it mean I'm an imposter, too?
My goodness
Tai Chi flows in harmony divine
Five elements perfectly align
True fire of Samadhi
ignites the gold
A perfect pill, its power unfolds
Swift and Uplift!
Why are you so scared?
We used to bathe in lava
like it's nothing
Hot! Hot!
Oh no!
It's the true fire of Samadhi
What are you looking at?
If anyone should eat this, it's me!
Yum
Let go of my father!
Freeze!
What a Spirit Pearl!
Perfect match with the Demon Orb
Ao Bing!
Freeze!
The Heart-Piercing Curse
Since I already knew
your true identities
how could I not have a backup plan?
This is impossible!
That curse is quite complex
When did you cast it?
Oh... That's why
the Ascension Spell took so long
You slipped in something
You old fart!
Even the Demon Orb
won't be able to break
the Heart-Piercing Curse so quick
A thousand spikes have pierced
through your nerves and veins
Forcing any movement
will only result in your body
being torn apart
No wonder
I couldn't sense any living aura
You were petrified
But being alive
you'll only hurt Nezha
The Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb
are precious treasures
I could've treated you well
but now you're only useful
for making pills
Ao Bing!
Father!
You... you're still alive!
It's the Heart-Piercing Curse
casted by Wuliang
And he was the one that
slaughtered Chentang Pass
framing it on the Loongs
Father
Nezha was deceived
Don't blame him
Whatever you want to do, do it to me
Leave my parents out of this
Killing you won't change anything
We're all doomed to die here
If anyone still holds grudges
be my guest
Brother
the Chan Sect has a noble reputation
how could you commit
such a horrible clanger?
Don't make more mistakes!
Why don't you go back
and confess to Master?
I'll plead for mercy on your behalf
You...
Indiscriminate fool!
If the immortals' place
in the world were secured
or you ungrateful slackers
were half as
diligent as the demons
I wouldn't have wasted
this much time and efforts!
Even if it leads to my own doom
and infamy
I did it for the eternal dominance
of Chan Sect
conscience...
My conscience is clear
Another one is done
I can't possibly eat any more
You should try some
Thanks
When my fins are done,
you should try some too
The claws are ready as well
We should swop and share
What's going on?
My body...
He's become a pill!
I'm still so young
I don't want to die
No, let me out
Help!
Stay calm!
Focus all your energy!
Hold on for as long as you can
Son!
Your power is greater than mine
You can get through
If you can hold out
until the heart-piercing curse fades
you'll have a chance to escape
The heart-piercing curse
takes at least six hours
I'm afraid...
I won't be able to last that long
- My lady
- Mom
Wake up, mom
Nezha, Nezha?
Nezha
I'm here, Mom
You guys must not give up
Don't worry about us
Try to stay focus
I'm fine, Mom
I don't feel the fire
Nothing kills you, kiddo
If I am correct
flames of the Demon Orb
and the true fire of Samadhi
share the same origin
Then the Tianyuan Cauldron
can't harm you
That's right
My mistake
Don't bother
This is just my avatar
As I suspected, the Demon Orb
is indestructible
No wonder the Supreme Lord had to
destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven
Nezha
I see you're a good son
How about I give you
a chance to prove that?
The Oblivion Pill
Swallow it
and I'll release your parents
What do you say?
I may be ruthless
but I always keep my promises
Otherwise,
all those elites of the demons
wouldn't swear loyalty to me
As long as you swallow it
I swear to Heaven
I won't harm your parents
What are you doing?
Using his parents' lives
to threaten a kid?
And you call yourself a god?
You aren't even worthy to be a human
Nezha
leave us be
You must live
Hold on until
the heart-piercing curse is broken
or until your two brothers find you
You really think
I can't kill the Demon Orb?
It's just a matter of time
Once you're dead
I have a hundred ways to destroy him
I just don't want to die for nothing
Why won't you let me?
Why won't you?
If your trade your life for ours
do you think we could live in peace?
Nezha
No, mom
It'll hurt you
It's okay
This is the end
I just want to hug you one last time
Mom
I guess I won't get
to see you grow up
From now on
you'll have to walk your own path
I... I'm useless
Useless
I was born a demon
and have always caused you pain
I wanted so badly
to make you proud
This is all my fault
I'm sorry, Mom
I'm sorry
Every day I spent with you
I was so happy
I never cared
whether you were an immortal
or a demon
All I know is
you are my son
Mommy
will always
love...
Nezha, stay calm!
Stop!
Your body will be torn apart!
The True Fire of Samadhi
has compensated for
the fire needed for body rebuilding
Nezha's physical form
is complete now!
Dad
take care of Mom
Help me break the cauldron!
Oh no!
They are absorbing the energy
of the Tianyuan Cauldron!
Roota Maxima!
Demon Hunters, by my command
march!
Father
you need to save your energy
for self-protection
We've been backing down
for far too long
We thought if we gave everything
then Wuliang would let us live
But in the end,
they still want us dead
If that's what they want
then we'll fight them to death!
Yes, let's fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
We can't let them out!
Do not give up!
Hang in there!
Make it...
break!
The cauldron!
My cauldron!
There goes the foundation
of Chan Sect!
Kill all these jerks!
Attack!
You ungrateful traitors
Can't tell right from wrong!
Roaring Loong Waves!
So those two minions of his
are monsters too
Demons, immortals...
it's all part of your trickery!
You despicable lowlife
How dare you oppose me!
Witness my true powers!
I'll give you two
one last chance
because I value talents
Surrender now
and I'll grant you immortality
Hell with immortality!
I'm all demon
So what?
You claim to be a guiding light
but all you do is bully the weak
and bring chaos to the world
You are the real evil!
Ignorant fools
the immortals rule the world
Siding with the powerful
is the only way out
Either accept that or
you'll have no place to run to
If there's no place to go
I will open up one myself!
If not accepted
I will overturn!
Master!
My face...
You...
You fools broke my Ageless Spell!
Old fart
Ba...back to the palace
Wait for me!
My father plans to lead the Loongs
deep into the ocean to hide
Now that your identity is exposed
why don't you come with us?
No
I've been hiding all my life
concealing myself
until there was nowhere to run
Now I finally know
how to face the world
Wuliang is one of the most
powerful immortals
and is trusted by the Supreme Lord
He may not fall so easily
Plus, immortals and demons
walk different paths
like water and fire
Immortals, demons...
Those are just excuses for
controlling those who are different
So what?
You think you can change that?
I want to try
Perhaps I'm too old
to fight against the world
Ao Bing
I know that
once you've made up your mind
you'll always follow through
My son
In the past
I've put too much burden on you
and never even
cared about what you think
I apologize
I only wanted to use my experience
to give you a good life
But now I see
the experience
of the older generation
is but the past
and may not be right for you
You must walk your own path
From now on
follow your heart
I knew you'd come back
Why?
Because we are both too young
Too young to fear
Master, your face...
It's fine
Crana already took care of it
The cauldron is destroyed
and the Chan Sect
no longer has a sure-win
We've committed
an unforgivable crime
We must act before the Master
comes out of seclusion
Come on, let's go see him
Is the holding cell hidden enough?
No one else will come here
The cell is also shielded from magic
And gate can only be opened
by you and the only guard
Slacking, dozing off
What's going on?
This gate
works with face-recognition
Since your appearance has changed
you need to re-register
Go ahead
Are you mocking me?
I curse you to sleep for ten years
You've suffered, my brother
It is you who have suffered, brother
Who... who did this to you?
Do you know why
I recruited you back then?
I needed a demon
When the Deification War comes
I will entrust you
with an important task
Delusional
Father!
Don't worry
He's still breathing
Let me place a curse on you
and your father will
live a comfortable life
at Yu Xu Palace
Your two guests have arrived
Think about it
The medicine is working
What should we do now?
Who else can open the gate?
Ten years...
Jinzha of Cloud Cave,
Wulong Mountain
Muzha of White Crane Cave,
Jiugong Mountain
reporting back to duty
Master, bear with me a little longer
I think it's enough
It seems
the left eye
still isn't swollen enough
Add some more
to the right cheek, too
Wait
Were you just laughing at me?
We wouldn't dare
Master, you're suffering
It pains our hearts
to see you like this
- Really?
- We solemnly swear
to heaven and earth
Alright, alright
I might have...
beaten too hard
What?
Don't worry
Put it on,
we'll come back when it heals
Master, you're meant for greatness
This is all for the future
of the Chan Sect
Let's try a few more times
we'll get it right eventually
Catch him! Don't let him go!
Quick! Apply the medicine!
Do it!
Let go of me!